Alright, in this lesson, we're going to implement this constructor.
This constructor follows the same process we discussed earlier.
It's the same.
First, we need to configure the audio input and output channels.
Then, it will generate the channel buffer here.
Ultimately, it will create the data interface handle here.
And use it over here.
Then, it will be used for the output as well.
And also for the input side.
We also created this device instance
This abstract device instance
We follow this method to proceed
First, we need to install the dependencies
These dependencies
Are for our audio framework
This one
Then we execute this command
Then let's take a look
It's right in here
It hasn't come over yet
Let's see why
First, let's take a look at this
This has been added here
Then we'll run this
Sure thing
It's fetching now
It has been fetched now
So, moving forward
we need to create a class member variable
this class member variable
we will create within this section
inside this abstract layer
why do we create it here
and why are we using this modifier
let’s take a look at this modifier now
there are these three types of modifiers in this class
Now there are three types.
First, this one is private.
The private one means you can only use it within the class, right?
Even its derived classes can't use it.
The private one is very confidential.
Then, PUBLIC is public.
You can call it from anywhere.
As long as it's instantiated, right?
You can call it.
So this modifier
is used between these two
it can be used in the derived class
it can also be used within its own class
meaning it's accessible in the current class
and its derived classes inherit it
and can use it as well
Why do we put these member variables into this framework
which is this abstract layer
Because this member variable
These member variables are all required within this framework
If we define them in the derived class
It's also fine
But the code becomes more redundant
So we put them here
Like these handles, right
These kinds of things
Like the output and input sample rates
These are all the elements we need in this framework, right?
We'll put all these in the equivalent of a chicken rib section.
Then, these are some items we'll be using shortly.
We define and place them here.
Then let's add a bit of image verification.
Alright, let's organize the header folder.
No errors, good.
Let's move on.
We need to declare the private member functions.
Let's add this member function.
This member function includes a few parts.
One is its initialization.
Then there's this section.
And then there's this part.
These three sections of the member function.
We'll place them in the specific implementation area.
We'll put this in the private members section.
Because we're calling it internally.
These functions are all called internally.
We don't need to make them public.
Because this is an internal implementation.
We don't need to expose it externally.
We can just put it in here.
Only within its internal scope.
Each one is different.
It's like within your framework.
This is the specific hardware implementation layer.
So, you'll use a different piece of hardware next time, right?
They are all different.
That's why it's placed at the specific implementation level.
This private member function will do the job.
Then,
This involves initializing the I2C channels.
We covered this before.
It's in this section.
It has been initialized here.
This one has been initialized.
And all of these have also been initialized.
So, we are now refactoring.
I won't go into the details here.
There is such a thing.
It initializes an IPNS channel.
Then it creates two handles.
These two handles will be used subsequently.
And
And then we need to initialize the ES8311 chip.
Because we need to use it on this platform.
So, we have to initialize it.
Also, the 7210 chip needs to be initialized as well.
This is right here.
There are three parts in here.
This is for the 7210.
And this is for the 8311.
Initializing it will generate this handle.
Finally, let's create this object here.
We'll minimize this.
Then let's add this image file.
Alright, let's implement these three member functions.
We'll implement them here.
Let's copy it over.
So, let's take a closer look.
Let's have a general look.
We covered this in the previous sections.
I won't go into the details.
Let's add this header.
Here, it's like we've created two handles for it.
We'll be using these handles next.
We've also created them in the previous section.
We won't go into the details here.
Fold it up.
Then, this part initializes the 8311.
This chip.
Then let's take a look at the parameter passing.
The first parameter is the IFC polymer.
This is initialized in the upper layer.
We just need to use it here.
Specifically, in the upper layer, you need to initialize whichever one you're using.
IFC, right?
Also, the IFC port is passed in here.
And this is where its address is specified.
The address is also configured by the hardware.
The address might be different, right?
This IPHONEC address usually refers to this type of chip, right?
It typically includes some wide-angle settings for configuration.
In our case, we don't specify it.
I'm not unaware of what your address is, you know.
This is determined by the development board.
We'll create a layer for the development board when the time comes.
We'll handle that part.
And this is the sound effect of its amplifier gear.
Then, we need to check if the amplifier gear is set to reverse.
That is, whether it triggers on a high level or a low current frequency.
This needs to be confirmed.
If it’s false, it means it triggers on a high level, which is non-inverted.
If it’s inverted,
it means the signal is inverted.
So, you would be triggering on a relatively low level.
Now, let’s add the header file here.
Let’s take a look at this.
So we passed in
we passed in this port
the port of IPHONEC
along with its address
and its handle
the handle of IPHONEC
here it creates a
this is also part of the framework
this is within the framework
He created this control.
Then he placed it inside here.
Then here, he created a GPIO operation.
The creation of the GPIO operation is for internal use.
We didn't just pass this, right?
Did we only pass the wide-angle feature?
He needs to configure the wide-angle feature.
To specifically operate the wide-angle feature.
So he needs to instantiate this.
Then we pass it in
We just need to send it there
For this mode
The first one is 8311
We only use its audio output here
That is, the DAC
The ADC is not used
If you also use the ADC
Then you configure this
This module uses both ADC and DAC.
But here we only use the DAC.
That is, the page output.
Then, it gets passed in here.
This one also gets passed in.
When I use it,
I don’t know how your board is configured, right?
You also used a transistor to perform the conversion.
After the conversion.
You might have reversed the logic battery.
In that case, I wouldn’t know.
I just need you to pass it in here.
You’ll make the decision when the time comes.
Then, configure this part, um,
Create one for 8311, ah,
Then we’ll pass this in.
That will instantiate the device object.
This is the abstract layer.
So we'll ultimately be implementing this.
Because within this framework,
we can directly use this component.
This is for the purpose of abstraction.
Then, this is equivalent to 148311.
The audio output has been abstracted out.
Then we'll abstract the ES7210 as well.
The abstraction process is the same for this one too.
Similarly, for the IPHONEC control.
Configure the control for the IPHONEC
This handle
Then we also pass in 7210
The IFC address
Pass it in
Then let's set this up.
Its microphone
For the microphone here
We can actually select three options
In the end, we didn't take the fourth one.
And this place is the same.
We input its type here.
It's a type of input state.
Then, we pass in an instance of the same here.
This is an instance of the abstract layer.
We instantiate it as an abstract layer.
Then, these three.
Should we call it here?
How do you call it?
First, here, the first time
The first call will definitely be to it, right?
Call it directly.
Pass this inside.
It will generate the handle.
Then we can use the handle, right?
And here, 8311
Inside here
Let's use this IFC here
Actually, we can pass it in here as well
Let's pass it here
For this AFC
We'll use this to pass it in
When instantiating
We'll pass it in here
This is the IFC
Let's pass it in this way
Then we'll pass this here.
And also, there's this 7311.
7210, that's it.
This one is the same as well.
We need to pass this in.
In this area, we have another thing to look at.
Here, we used a certain tool.
We used this, but we haven't initialized it yet.
This is where we discussed generating the data interface.
The handle
we call it to generate
So, for this
we need to initialize it here
generate this
where do we write this in here
because this is like between them
we can just write it here
we write this here to call this, right
Call this function
This function, right?
Create a channel for this data
We set this as a sending channel
One for receiving and one for sending
And we use IFS number 0
After it's created
We can use it here
It can be used internally
This is the entire process.
That completes the initialization.
Let's take a look.
Next, we need to make a change here.
We added an extra parameter just now.
We'll move this parameter to the header file.
Let's add one here.
That should do it.
Now, let's check it out.
What else is in here?
Ah.
In that case,
we're essentially dealing with this kind of combination,
this audio input and output,
which addresses its underlying structure, right?
We pass the constructor function in,
and then we proceed like this,
then let's take a look at what we have here.
There's one more thing
which is, we're here
here we're using a sampling rate, right
let me check
this should be here
the sampling rate, correct
regarding the sampling rate
we only defined it here
but haven't initialized it
how do we initialize it
we need to pass this in, right
in the constructor, right
we pass it in the constructor
so we need to add this here
use this, right
this operation to
output the sampling rate
also add it in
this is what we pass in, right
this and this, right
and the other parameters are used, right
the other parameters are all used
just these two parameters
we need to move this up here first
so we can use it inside, right
otherwise, you haven't initialized it, right
I haven't set it up yet
this needs to be added
we'll cover the rest in the next class
so in this class, we'll get these initializations done
in the next class, we'll specifically cover these
the audio output
audio input, reading and outputting audio
playing audio
and also the gears
let's write these down
that's it for this class